Catherine Gu

Design Internship (858) 602-9728 cgu@ucsd.com San Diego, CA Enthusiastic, detail-oriented undergraduate interested in gaining experience in human design and interaction. I have worked in many group projects that go through the entire design processes up until a final prototype. I have engaged in many upper division courses that teach how to design in a user-oriented manner.



Skills:

- Proficient in Figma
- Writing code in Java, Python, C, HTML + CSS
- Developing prototypes
- Analyzing user behavior in prototype testing
- User Experience
- Storyboarding
- Great team player



Education:

University of California San Diego

Cognitive Science Major w/ Specialization in Design and Interaction, 3.98 GPA

2020-Present | San Diego, CA

RELEVANT COURSEWORK

- Cognitive Perspectives
- Cognitive Ethnography
- Cognitive Design Studio
- Usability and Information Architecture
- Design of Everyday Things
- Cognitive Consequences of Technology
- Introduction to Research
 Methods



Design Portfolio:

https://catherinegu16.github.io/Design-Portfolio/



Work Experience:

Fidelity Talent Source (Feb 2022 - Present)

Data Entry Associate

- Accurately identified emotions in recorded customer calls through tone and content
- Annotated calls into Fidelity database
- Proactively completed trainings needed
- Maintained customer privacy and handled sensitive information
- Aided in the training of an AI project

Kumon Math and Reading Center, San Diego, CA

(Nov 2019 - Oct 2020)

Assistant Instructor

- Guided students in developing independence in their learning
- Multitasked grading student work, doing flashcards with students, assisting students, keeping classroom on task
- Oversaw students in classroom and common areas to monitor, enforce rules and support lead teacher.